So, uh, your first sexual experience was with a woman?
那麼，呃，你的第一次性經驗是和女人發生的？
All right, I was 15. It was my best friend, Ruth,
好吧，當時我 15 歲。那是我最好的朋友，露絲，
and we got drunk on that hard cider,
我們喝醉了烈性蘋果酒，
and then suddenly, I don't know, we were making out.
然後突然之間，我不知道，我們就親熱了。
Tell it again.
再說一次。
Seriously.
嚴重地。
I mean, is that woman capable of talking about anything else but sex?
我的意思是，那個女人除了性還能談論其他事情嗎？
Yeah, sure. Well, you know, earlier, she was talking about geography.
是的，當然。嗯，你知道，早些時候她在談論地理。
Joey, she was listing the countries she's done it in.
喬伊，她列出了她做過的國家。
Well, I think we all learned something.
嗯，我想我們都學到了一些東西。
Hey, you guys, look what I found. Look at this.
嘿，夥計們，看看我發現了什麼。看看這個。
That's my mom's writing. Look.
這是我媽媽寫的。看。
Me and Frank and Phoebe, graduation 1965.
我、法蘭克和菲比，1965 年畢業。
Do you know what that means?
你知道這意味著什麼嗎？
That you're actually 50?
原來你已經50歲了？
No, no, that's not me, Phoebe. That's her pal, Phoebe.
不，不，那不是我，菲比。那是她的朋友菲比。
According to her high school yearbook, they were like BFF.
根據她的高中年鑑，他們就像最好的朋友。
Best friends forever.
永遠最好的朋友。
Oh, that's great. That's so cool.
哦，那太好了。太酷了。
I know. So this woman probably could, like, has all kinds of stories about my parents.
我知道。所以這個女人可能有各種關於我父母的故事。
And she might even know, like, where my dad is.
她甚至可能知道我爸爸在哪裡。
So I looked her up, and she lives out by the beach.
於是我查了一下她，她住在海邊。
So maybe this weekend we could go to the beach.
所以也許這個週末我們可以去海灘。
Yeah, we could.
是的，我們可以。
Shoot, I can't go. I have to work.
開槍吧，我不能走。我必須工作。
That's too bad.
那太糟糕了。
Oh, big fat bummer.
哦，大胖子。
So great. Okay, tomorrow we're going to drive out to Montauk.
太棒了。好的，明天我們要開車去蒙托克。
Hey, Bonnie had sex there.
嘿，邦妮在那裡做愛。
When it hasn't been your day, week, or month, or even your year.
當這不是你的一天、一週、一個月，甚至不是你的一年。
But I'll be there for you.
但我會在你身邊。
When the rain starts to pour.
當雨開始傾盆而下。
I'll be there for you.
我會在那等你。
Like I've been there before.
就像我以前去過那裡一樣。
I'll be there for you.
我會在那等你。
So there I'll be too.
那我也會在那裡。
Hey.
嘿。
Joey would be right down. He's just looking for his mask.
喬伊馬上就下來了。他只是在尋找他的面具。
Oh, his swim mask?
哦，他的游泳面罩？
No, his gorilla mask.
不，是他的大猩猩面具。
He wears it in the ocean to scare off the fish.
他在海裡戴著它來嚇跑魚。
Would you look at that?
你會看一下嗎？
Never going to find a boyfriend again.
再也不會找男朋友了。
Die an old maid.
死得像個老處女。
You're not going to die an old maid.
你不會以老處女的身份死去。
Maybe an old spinster cook.
也許是個老處女廚師。
Thanks.
謝謝。
Hey, no, besides, worse comes to worse, I'll be your boyfriend.
嘿，不，更糟的是，我會成為你的男朋友。
Yeah, right.
是的，對。
Why is that so funny?
為什麼這麼好笑？
You made a joke, right?
你開了個玩笑，對嗎？
So I laughed.
於是我笑了。
A little too hard.
有點太難了。
What am I, not a boyfriend material?
我不是男友的料是什麼？
No.
不。
You're Chandler.
你是錢德勒。
You know.
你知道。
Chandler.
錢德勒。
Okay, so we've established my name and hit me.
好吧，我們已經確定了我的名字並打了我。
But theoretically, you know, I mean, say we weren't friends.
但理論上，你知道，我的意思是，假設我們不是朋友。
Say it's a blind date.
說是相親吧。
I show up at your door, and I'm like, hey, nice to meet you.
我出現在你家門口，我說，嘿，很高興見到你。
Hey.
嘿。
I'd probably be scared of the guy using a fake voice.
我可能會害怕那個用假聲音的人。
Hey.
嘿。
Oh, good, you bought food.
哦，太好了，你買了食物。
No, just my luggage.
不，只是我的行李。
Hey.
嘿。
Hey, guys.
嘿，夥計們。
Yes.
是的。
I am having the best karma this week.
這週我的業力最好。
First I find this woman who knew my parents,
首先我找到了這個認識我父母的女人，
and then my client with the fuzzy back
然後是我背部毛茸茸的客戶
gives me his beach house.
把他的海濱別墅給了我。
What about that bike messenger you hit?
你撞到的那個腳踏車信差怎麼了？
Oh, I wasn't talking about his karma.
哦，我不是說他的業力。
Hey.
嘿。
Hey, check out the hat.
嘿，看看帽子。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
I know that hat.
我認識那頂帽子。
I was taken aboard that hat.
我被帶上了那頂帽子。
They did experiments on me.
他們對我做了實驗。
I can't have children.
我不能生孩子。
Seriously, where did you get the hat?
說真的，你從哪裡得到的帽子？
Russ gave it to me.
拉斯把它給了我。
Oh, I think she looks good.
哦，我覺得她看起來不錯。
Oh, thank you.
哦，謝謝。
Did he buy it for you or win it for you?
他是為你買的還是為你贏得的？
Excuse me, my fashion-impaired friends.
對不起，我那些時尚達人的朋友們。
I am here to tell you that hats are back.
我來這裡是為了告訴你帽子又回來了。
And this time they've ganged up
而這次他們又聯合起來了
and formed one giant super hat.
並形成了一頂巨大的超級帽。
Go, go, go.
去！去！去。
Yeah, now everybody wants to be under the hat.
是的，現在每個人都想躲在帽子底下。
Oy.
哎喲。
What's with all this sand?
這些沙子是怎麼回事？
Uh, yeah.
呃，是的。
Bob said there might be plant damage.
鮑伯說植物可能會受損。
Either that or he has a really big cat.
要嘛他有一隻很大的貓。
Uh, you know what this reminds me of?
呃，你知道這讓我想起了什麼嗎？
Um, why couldn't I be your boyfriend?
嗯，為什麼我不能成為你的男朋友？
Are you still on that?
你還在這上面嗎？
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
Did you let it go already?
你已經放下了嗎？
Thank you, Joey.
謝謝你，喬伊。
But you'd go out with me, right?
但你會跟我一起出去，對嗎？
No.
不。
It is the same as with Chandler.
這與錢德勒的情況相同。
We're friends.
我們是朋友。
Well, let's say we were the last two guys on the face of the planet
好吧，假設我們是地球上最後兩個人
and you had a gun to your head.
你的頭被槍指著。
Which one would you pick?
你會選擇哪一個？
Which one of you has the gun to my head?
你們誰用槍指著我的頭？
Well, yes, it's kind of an unusual house.
嗯，是的，這是一棟不尋常的房子。
It has, um, three beautiful bedrooms
它有，嗯，三間漂亮的臥室
and, uh, no baths.
而且，呃，沒有浴缸。
But, you know, the ocean is right there.
但是，你知道，海洋就在那裡。
Well...
出色地...
Uh, oh, hang on a second.
呃，哦，等一下。
Come in, come in.
進來吧，進來吧。
All right, so think about it and call me back.
好吧，你考慮一下然後回電給我。
Are you, uh, Phoebe Abbott?
你是，呃，菲比·阿博特嗎？
Uh, yes.
呃，是的。
Surprise, Phoebe Abbott.
驚喜，菲比阿博特。
I'm your best friend's daughter.
我是你最好朋友的女兒。
You're Irwin's daughter?
你是歐文的女兒？
No, I mean your old best friend.
不，我是說你最好的老朋友。
Here.
這裡。
Lily from high school, remember?
高中時的莉莉，還記得嗎？
Oh, God, Lily.
哦，上帝，莉莉。
Yes, of course I remember Lily.
是的，我當然記得莉莉。
I...
我...
Then you must be...
那你一定是...
Phoebe. Phoebe.
菲比。菲比。
Phoebe, yeah. She named me after you, I guess.
菲比，是的。我猜她以你的名字命名我。
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
Wow. Well, look, there's Frank.
哇。嗯，看，弗蘭克來了。
Yeah, yes, yes, yes!
是啊是啊是啊！
That's my dad, it's Frank!
那是我爸爸，是弗蘭克！
Yeah, I'm sorry, I'm getting all flingy.
是的，對不起，我變得輕浮了。
Oh, okay, okay.
噢，好吧，好吧。
Take it easy. If you want, there's cookies on the counter.
別緊張。如果你想要的話，櫃檯上有餅乾。
Or sangria, I could make sangria.
或者桑格利亞汽酒，我可以做桑格利亞汽酒。
No, no, I'm sorry.
不，不，對不起。
Cookies are good, thanks.
餅乾很好吃，謝謝。
Oh.
哦。
Well, so, um,
嗯，所以，嗯，
anyway, um,
無論如何，嗯，
I've been looking for my father,
我一直在尋找我的父親
and, um, have you heard from him
還有，嗯，你有他的訊息嗎
or seen him?
或見過他嗎？
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
哦，不，對不起。
I guess I lost track of everybody after high school.
我想高中畢業後我就失去了所有人的聯絡。
Oh. Okay.
哦。好的。
Well,
嗯，
so tell me everything about my parents.
所以告訴我關於我父母的一切。
Everything.
一切。
Oh, well, you know, we were always together.
哦，好吧，你知道，我們一直在一起。
In fact, the other kids had a nickname
事實上，其他孩子有一個暱稱
for the three of us.
對我們三個人來說。
Oh, what? What was it?
哦，什麼？那是什麼？
The three losers.
三個失敗者。
Oh, poor Lily.
噢，可憐的莉莉。
Oh.
哦。
You know, I heard about what happened.
你知道，我聽說了發生的事情。
That must have been just terrible for you,
這對你來說一定是太可怕了
losing your mother that way.
就這樣失去了你的母親。
Yeah, no, it was great.
是的，不，那太棒了。
Hey, you know what a really good rainy day game is?
嘿，你知道什麼是真正優秀的雨天遊戲嗎？
What?
什麼？
I mean, naked game.
我的意思是，赤裸裸的遊戲。
Strip poker. We should totally play strip poker.
脫衣撲克。我們完全應該玩脫衣撲克。
But are you crazy?
但你瘋了嗎？
Come on, when you go away, you have to play.
來吧，當你離開時，你必須玩。
It's, like, a law.
這就像一條法律。
No, it's not a law.
不，這不是法律。
As long as it stays attached to that tax reform bill,
只要它繼續遵守稅改法案，
it never will be, mister.
永遠不會，先生。
All done.
全部完成。
Thank you.
謝謝。
Okay, who's next?
好吧，下一個是誰？
No.
不。
No way.
決不。
Come on, please. I'm bored.
來吧，請。我很無聊。
You let me do it once before.
你之前讓我做過一次。
Yeah, well, if, uh,
是的，好吧，如果，呃，
if that's the rule this weekend...
如果這是這個週末的規則的話...
Yeah, just come on.
是的，來吧。
Take it like a man, Ross.
像個男人一樣對待它，羅斯。
No, no.
不，不。
Oh, come on.
哦，來吧。
Big bullies?
大惡霸？
Oh, ow!
哦，哦！
No, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不。
No!
不！
Oh, hey.
哦，嘿。
Hey.
嘿。
So how are we doing?
那我們怎麼樣？
Bored and bored.
無聊又無聊。
Hey, you know what?
嘿，你知道嗎？
Naked card game's never boring.
裸體紙牌遊戲永遠不會無聊。
No!
不！
So what's Phoebe like?
那麼菲比到底是什麼樣的人呢？
I'm kind, caring, and sweet.
我很善良、很體貼、很可愛。
What's Monica like?
莫妮卡是個什麼樣的人？
Uh, no, the other Phoebe.
呃，不，是另一個菲比。
The one you went to go see.
你去看的那個。
Oh, I think she knows where my dad is.
哦，我想她知道我爸爸在哪裡。
That's cool.
這很酷。
Well, where is he?
那麼，他在哪裡？
She was pretending like she hasn't heard from him in years,
她假裝好幾年沒有收到他的訊息了
but I found this picture on her fridge.
但我在她的冰箱上發現了這張照片。
And look, isn't this what he would look like now?
你看，這不就是他現在的樣子嗎？
Totally familiar.
完全熟悉。
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Well, why would she lie to you?
那麼，她為什麼要騙你呢？
I don't know, but we're having dinner tomorrow night,
idk 但我們明天晚上要吃晚餐
so I figured she's gonna tell me then.
所以我想她會告訴我。
You know, maybe she just wanted to give him time
你知道，也許她只是想給他時間
to buy me presents.
給我買禮物。
I don't know.
我不知道。
So, you're all bored?
那麼，你們都無聊了嗎？
Oh, yes.
哦是的。
All right, I'm gonna close my eyes
好吧，我要閉上眼睛
and point to someone, and whoever I point to
並指向某人，無論我指向誰
has to come up with something fun for us to do,
必須想出一些有趣的事情讓我們去做，
and we have to do it.
我們必須這樣做。
Okay, all right, fan out, fan out.
好吧，好吧，扇出，扇出。
Okay.
好的。
Ooh, you know, we could just do this.
哦，你知道，我們可以這樣做。
Okay, um, we all have to
好吧，嗯，我們都必須
play strip poker?
玩脫衣撲克？
Oh, yes!
哦是的！
Chandler, why all of a sudden
錢德，為什麼突然
do you want to play strip poker?
你想玩脫衣撲克嗎？
I think because of margaritas three, four, and nine.
我想是因為瑪格麗特三杯、四杯和九杯。
Strip happy days game?
脫衣快樂日子遊戲？
Well, I couldn't find any cards,
額，沒找到卡啊
so it was either this or a stripped bag
所以要嘛是這個，要嘛是一個脫光的袋子
of old knitting stuff.
舊針織品。
Got it.
知道了。
Okay.
好的。
Fonzie gives you two thumbs up.
方齊向你豎起兩個大拇指。
Collect two cool points.
收集兩個酷點。
Yeah.
是的。
All right, if you get five cool points,
好吧，如果你得到五個酷點，
you get to make someone take off one item of clothing.
你可以讓某人脫掉一件衣服。
It hasn't happened yet, but we're all very excited.
雖然這一切還沒發生，但我們都非常興奮。
Okay, come on.
好吧，來吧。
Daddy needs a new pair of electromagnetic
爸爸需要一雙新的電磁
microscopes for the prehistoric forensics department.
史前法醫學部門的顯微鏡。
Okay.
好的。
Take Pinky Tuscadero up to
搭乘 Pinky Tuscadero 前往
inspiration point. Collect three cool points.
靈感點。收集三個酷點。
Yeah!
是的！
Which gives me five, and let's see
這給了我五個，讓我們看看
who is going to lose their clothes.
誰會失去衣服。
Um, I think I pick
嗯，我想我選
our strip poker sponsor,
我們的脫衣撲克贊助商，
Mr. Joey Tribbiani.
喬伊·特里比亞尼先生。
All right, relax.
好吧，放鬆點。
It's just a shoe.
這只是一隻鞋。
Your band is playing at Arnold's.
你的樂團正在阿諾德表演。
Collect three cool points.
收集三個酷點。
Which means I have five,
這意味著我有五個，
and that means I get Joey's boxers.
這意味著我得到了喬伊的平角內褲。
Fine.
美好的。
Gang up on me.
聯合起來圍攻我。
I got you all right where I want you.
我在我想要你的地方找到了你。
Come on, take them off.
來吧，把它們脫掉。
Actually, you know, it's kind of cold,
事實上，你知道，天氣有點冷，
so how about I keep my boxers on
那我繼續穿平角內褲怎麼樣
and give you all a peek at the good stuff?
並給大家看看好東西？
All right, I'm gonna make more margaritas.
好吧，我要做更多的瑪格麗塔酒。
Well, hey, what are you doing,
嗯，嘿，你在做什麼，
trying to get me drunk?
想把我灌醉嗎？
I'm just making margaritas.
我只是在做瑪格麗塔酒。
I think I'll help her out.
我想我會幫助她。
What?
什麼？
What is going on here?
這是怎麼回事？
What?
什麼？
Are you painting his toenails?
你幫他塗腳趾甲嗎？
Oh, come on.
哦，來吧。
Chasing him around the room?
在房間裡追著他？
Monica, please.
莫妮卡，請。
He's totally flirting with you, too.
他也完全在跟你調情。
He is, isn't he?
他是，不是嗎？
I don't know. I don't know.
我不知道。我不知道。
I mean, maybe it's just being here
我的意思是，也許只是在這裡
at the beach together,
一起在海灘，
or I don't know,
或者我不知道，
but it's like something...
但它就像某件事...
Hey!
嘿！
Hi, Bonnie.
嗨，邦妮。
My boss let me off early,
老闆提前讓我下班了
so I took the train.
所以我坐火車。
What are you guys doing?
你們在做什麼？
We're playing strip happy days game.
我們正在玩脫衣舞快樂時光遊戲。
Cool. I'll catch up.
涼爽的。我會趕上的。
So, you still don't think, um,
所以，你仍然不認為，嗯，
boyfriend material?
男友材質？
Huh?
啊？
Saw you checking me out
看到你在檢查我
during the game last night.
昨晚的比賽期間。
You didn't even take off your pants.
你連褲子都沒脫。
Yeah, well, lucky for you.
是的，好吧，你很幸運。
What?
什麼？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Well,
嗯，
is everybody else having just the best time?
其他人都在享受最美好的時光嗎？
Shh.
噓。
Joey's asleep.
喬伊睡著了。
After he passed out,
他昏倒後，
we put the sand around him
我們把沙子放在他周圍
to keep him warm.
讓他保持溫暖。
Well, I assume
好吧，我假設
the, uh, happy couple
這對幸福的夫婦
isn't up yet.
還沒起來。
Did you guys hear them last night?
昨晚你們聽到了嗎？
Oh, yeah. I don't know what they were doing,
哦，是的。我不知道他們在做什麼
but at one point, sea turtles
但在某一時刻，海龜
actually came up to the house.
真的來到了房子前。
Morning.
早晨。
Hey.
嘿。
How'd everybody sleep?
大家睡得怎麼樣？
Oh, great. Like a log.
哦，太好了。就像一根木頭。
Us, too.
我們也是。
I'm going for a walk.
我要去散步。
Good morning.
早安。
Nice breasts, by the way.
順便說一下，胸部不錯。
Hey, what happened to you?
嘿，你怎麼了？
Oh, uh, nothing. I just
哦，呃，沒什麼。我只是
felt like hanging out here and reading.
感覺就像在這裡閒逛並閱讀。
The water was so great.
水太大了。
We jumped off this pier, and my suit
我們從這個碼頭跳下來，我的衣服
came off.
下來了。
Sorry I missed that.
抱歉我錯過了。
Yeah, Joey and Chandler sure are funny.
是的，喬伊和錢德勒確實很有趣。
I think I brought back half the beach
我想我帶回了一半的海灘
in my hair. It was so much easier
在我的頭髮裡。事情變得容易多了
when I used to shave my head.
當我以前剃頭的時候。
You know,
你知道，
I gotta tell you, I just loved
我得告訴你，我只是愛過
your look when you were bald.
你禿頭時的樣子
Really?
真的嗎？
Because I think about shaving it all off again
因為我想再次把它全部剃掉
sometimes. Really?
有時。真的嗎？
Yeah. I mean, you
是的。我的意思是，你
definitely should do that.
絕對應該這樣做。
You know what? I should do it. Yeah.
你知道嗎？我應該這麼做。是的。
You know what? Thank you, Rachel.
你知道嗎？謝謝你，雷切爾。
You are so cool. Oh, stop.
你真酷。哦，停下來。
I'm gonna shave that head.
我要把那個頭剃掉。
All right.
好的。
I know I've asked you this before.
我知道我以前問過你這個問題。
A hundred times before!
之前一百次了！
How am I not right for you?
我怎麼不適合你呢？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I like guys like Richard
我喜歡像理查德這樣的人
or Pete, before he went insane.
或者皮特，在他發瘋之前。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Somebody more mature.
一個更成熟的人。
Oh, so I'm not mature enough
哦，所以我還不夠成熟
for you? Monica needs somebody
為你？莫妮卡需要有人
more mature.
更加成熟。
What's the matter, Pheebs?
怎麼了，菲比？
She canceled. My name say
她取消了。我的名字說
canceled on me. What? Yeah, she claims
對我取消了。什麼？是的，她聲稱
she had to go out of town suddenly.
她不得不突然出城。
She's avoiding me. She doesn't want to tell me where
她在躲避我。她不想告訴我在哪裡
my father is. She knows, and she won't tell me.
我父親是。她知道，但她不會告訴我。
Oh, Pheebs, that sucks.
噢，菲比斯，這太糟糕了。
Yeah, well, don't off Pheebs. That sucks me yet.
是啊，好吧，別離開菲比。那還讓我很糟糕。
Where are you going? Well, she's out of town,
你要去哪裡？嗯，她出城了，
so there's gotta be something in her house
所以她家裡一定有什麼東西
that tells me where my father is.
這告訴我我父親在哪裡。
Uh, Pheebs, some people call it breaking and
呃，Pheebs，有些人稱之為破壞性的
entering. Well, are any of those
進入。嗯，其中有嗎？
people here? Oh, no.
這裡的人？哦，不。
Okay. Look, I'll
好的。你看，我會
do something nice, okay? I'll
做點好事，好嗎？我會
fill her ice trays.
把她的冰盤裝滿。
Hey, everybody.
嘿，大家。
Wow!
哇！
Ha!
哈!
Ha! Ha! Look
哈!哈!看
what you did.
你做了什麼。
You want to touch it?
你想觸控它嗎？
No, but it's great.
不，但這很棒。
Come on. Touch it.
快點。觸控它。
Okay.
好的。
You can feel all the bones in your skull.
您可以感覺到頭骨中的所有骨頭。
No, that's...
不，那是...
Hi. Hi.
你好。你好。
I was having a little chat with Bonnie, and
我正在和邦妮閒聊，然後
guess what? She happened to
你猜怎麼著？她碰巧
bring up, you know, who was behind the whole
提起，你知道，誰是整個事件的幕後黑手
head shaving idea. And now, who was it?
剃頭的想法。而現在，是誰？
Oh, that's right, that's right. It was you.
噢，對了，對了。是你。
That was her idea.
這是她的主意。
I just...
我只是...
gave her a nudge. She said you gave her the
輕輕推了她一下。她說你給了她
razor.
剃刀。
Hey. Hey.
嘿。嘿。
So, anyone up for a midnight dip in the
所以，任何想要在午夜暢泳的人
ocean? Uh, I'm good.
海洋？呃，我很好。
No, thanks. Okay, I'll see you in a bit. Okay,
不，謝謝。好的，一會兒見。好吧，
have fun. Bye.
玩得開心。再見。
See? She doesn't look that bad.
看？她看起來沒那麼糟。
You can see the moonlight
你可以看到月光
bouncing off her head.
從她的頭上彈開。
What the hell were you thinking? I don't
你到底在想什麼？我不
know. You don't know? Rach, you balded my
知道。你不知道嗎？瑞秋，你把我的禿了
girlfriend. All right.
女朋友。好的。
Ross,
羅斯，
do you think it's easy for me to see
你覺得我很容易看出來嗎
you with somebody else? You know what?
你和別人在一起嗎？你知道嗎？
Hey, you're the one who ended it, remember? Yeah,
嘿，你是結束這一切的人，記得嗎？是的，
because I was mad at you, not because I
因為我生你的氣，不是因為我
stopped loving you.
不再愛你了。
You still love me?
你還愛我嗎？
No.
不。
You still love me?
你還愛我嗎？
Yeah, so,
是的，所以，
you love me. No.
你愛我。不。
What does this mean? What are you...
這意味著什麼？你是什​​麼...
I mean, do you want to
我的意思是，你想
get back together? No.
複合嗎？不。
Maybe.
或許。
I don't... I don't know.
我不……我不知道。
Ross,
羅斯，
I still can't forgive you for what you
我還是無法原諒你的所作所為
did.
做過。
I just... but sometimes when I'm with you,
我只是...但有時當我和你在一起時
I just... I feel... What?
我只是...我感覺...什麼？
I just...
我只是...
I feel...
我覺得...
I just...
我只是...
What?
什麼？
I feel...
我覺得...
No!
不！
I don't care. I'm not playing
我不在乎。我沒玩
one-on-one strip poker with you for
與您一對一脫衣撲克
practice.
實踐。
We don't make cards.
我們不做卡片。
Good night.
晚安。
I'm going upstairs.
我要上樓了。
Alright.
好吧。
Want to play strip poker for practice?
想玩脫衣撲克練習嗎？
Ow!
噢！
My pants!
我的褲子！
Okay.
好的。
Shh!
噓！
Ah! No!
啊!不！
Ow! It's me! It's me!
噢！這就是我！這就是我！
I didn't want to make any noise!
我不想發出任何聲音！
Then don't break in!
那就別闖了！
I'm sorry.
對不起。
What are you doing here?
你在這裡做什麼？
I... I...
我...我...
came to fill your ice cube tray.
來填充你的冰塊託盤。
What?
什麼？
Um...
嗯...
Okay.
好的。
Okay, look.
好吧，看一下。
I took this picture
我拍了這張照片
from your fridge, okay? Because I know
從你的冰箱拿出來，好嗎？因為我知道
that this is my father. Yeah, this is
這是我的父親。是的，這是
Frank Buffay, and you were standing right there
弗蘭克·布菲，你就站在那裡
next to him. Now, look, I
在他旁邊。現在，看，我
deserve to know where I came from, alright?
應該知道我來自哪裡，好嗎？
So if you can help me find my father,
所以如果你能幫我找到我的父親
then you should. Otherwise,
那你應該。否則，
you're just mean.
你只是刻薄。
So just tell me the truth.
所以請告訴我真相。
Alright.
好吧。
The man in that picture
那張照片裡的男人
is Chuck Mangione.
是查克·曼吉奧內。
My father is Chuck Mangione?
我的父親是查克·曼吉奧內？
No, no, that's
不不不，那是
just Chuck Mangione. I sold
只是查克·曼吉奧內。我賣了
him a house last year.
去年買了一棟房子。
And I'm very sorry, but I really
我很抱歉，但我真的
don't know where your father is.
不知道你父親在哪裡。
And that's the truth.
這就是事實。
Oh.
哦。
But, um, you're right.
但是，嗯，你是對的。
I think that
我認為
that person should know where they come from.
那個人應該知道他們來自哪裡。
Which is why
這就是為什麼
I, uh...
我，呃…
Uh...
呃...
Okay.
好的。
I'm your mother.
我是你的母親。
Eh?
呃？
See, you know, I wanted to
你看，你知道，我想要
tell you yesterday, but I just...
昨天告訴你了，但我只是...
You know, I felt all floopy, and...
你知道，我覺得渾身無力，而且…
I'm telling you,
我告訴你，
you guys are totally getting back together.
你們完全複合了。
That's not true. She doesn't even know what she wants.
那不是真的。她甚至不知道自己想要什麼。
Rachel's still mad about the whole thing.
雷切爾仍然對整件事感到生氣。
Okay, well, then, you gotta back away, alright?
好吧，那麼，你得回去了，好嗎？
You don't need that kind of hurt.
你不需要那樣的傷害。
Take it from a guy who's...
從一個人那裡拿走，他是...
never had a long-term
從未有過長期的
relationship.
關係。
I know, but...
我知道，但是...
I really wanna go up there and finish that kiss.
我真的很想上去完成那個吻。
Hey!
嘿！
You guys, the water's great.
你們，水真好。
You should really go in.
你真的應該進去。
Oh, uh, no thanks.
哦，呃，不用了，謝謝。
I just had an M&M.
我剛剛吃了一顆 M&M 巧克力豆。
Okay. Well, goodnight.
好的。嗯，晚安。
Goodnight.
晚安。
Don't be too long.
不要太長。
Okey-dokey.
好吧，好吧。
There is not one hair on that head.
那頭上一根頭髮都沒有。
Hey, it'll grow back, right?
嘿，它會再長出來的，對吧？
And she's really fun,
而且她真的很有趣
and she's cool, and...
而且她很酷，而且...
I'm finally moving on, you know?
我終於要繼續前進了，你知道嗎？
I mean, getting over Rachel was so...
我的意思是，克服雷切爾是如此......
You know?
你知道？
You know, I'm finally feeling sane again.
你知道，我終於恢復理智了。
And now if I go up there and I kiss her,
現在如果我上去親吻她，
and...
還有…
God, I wanna kiss her, and...
天哪，我想吻她，然後…
And it doesn't work out, right?
而且這行不通，對吧？
Do I really wanna put myself through that again?
我真的想讓自己再經歷一次嗎？
So let me get this straight.
讓我說清楚。
If you go with Bonnie tonight,
如果你今晚和邦妮一起去
you're doing the smart, healthy thing and moving on.
你正在做明智、健康的事情並繼續前進。
Yeah.
是的。
And if you go with Rachel,
如果你和雷切爾一起去
Bonnie's free tonight.
邦妮今晚有空。
Hi.
你好。
Hi there.
你好呀。
That's that weird voice again.
又是那個奇怪的聲音。
Okay, okay.
好吧，好吧。
Let me try it again.
讓我再試一次。
You're gonna wanna date this next guy, I swear.
我發誓你會想和下一個約會的。
Okay, come on.
好吧，來吧。
I can only do it with the voice now.
我現在只能用聲音來做。
Okay, okay, come on, come on.
好吧好吧，來吧，來吧。
Close the door, close the door.
關門，關門。
Hi, I'm Dorf.
嗨，我是多爾夫。
You date for the evening.
你們約會晚上。
Oh, come on, Dorf on dating?
哦，拜託，多爾夫約會了嗎？
That's good stuff!
那可是好東西啊！